Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Records, 1837 - 2013
Bentley Historical Library
- Director's Files, 1905-2013
  - Topical Files, 1905-1999
    - 1957-1967
      - ALA Washington Office
        - 1963-1964 (Box 82)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 82)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 82)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 82)
      - Amherst College
        - 1959-1961 (Box 82)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 82)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 82)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 82)
        - 1965-1967 (Box 82)
      - Area Studies Liaison Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 82)
      - Association of College and Research Libraries
        - 1957-1958 (Box 82)
        - 1958-1962 (Box 82)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 82)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 82)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 82)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 82)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 82)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 82)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 82)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 82)
      - ACRL Questionnaire
        - 1957-1958 (Box 82)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 82)
      - ACRL-ARL Advisory Committee on Planning of College and University Buildings
        - 1959-1960 (Box 82)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 82)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 82)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 82)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 82)
      - Association of Research Libraries
        - 1957-1958 (Box 82)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 82)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 83)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 83)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 83)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 83)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 83)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 83)
        - 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 83)
        - 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 83)
      - ARL Board of Directors
        - 1961-1962 (Box 83)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 83)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 83)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 83)
      - ARL Committee on Catalog Code Revision
        - 1961-1962 (Box 83)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 83)
      - ARL Committee on Near Eastern Materials
        - 1957-1958 (Box 84)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 84)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 84)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 84)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 84)
      - ARL Committee on Publishing Dissertations
        - 1958-1959 (Box 84)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 84)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 84)
      - ARL Committee on World List of Serials, 1966-1967 (Box 84)
      - ARL Farmington Plan
        - 1957-1958 (Box 84)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 84)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 84)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 84)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 84)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 84)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 84)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 84)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 84)
      - Bowdoin College
        - 1962-1964 (Box 84)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 84)
      - Brown University, 1956-1961 (Box 84)
      - Butler University, 1959-1961 (Box 84)
      - California, University of
        - 1957-1958 (Box 84)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 84)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 84)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 84)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 84)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 84)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 84)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 84)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 84)
      - California, University at Los Angeles
        - 1957-1958 (Box 84)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 84)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 84)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 84)
        - 1962-1964 (Box 84)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 84)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 84)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 84)
      - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1957-1958 (Box 84)
      - Case Institute of Technology.-Western Reserve University, 1966-1967 (Box 85)
      - Center for Research Libraries
        - 1964-1965 (Box 85)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 85)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 85)
      - Central Michigan University, 1959-1960 (Box 85)
      - Chicago, University of
        - 1958-1964 (Box 85)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 85)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 85)
      - Christmas Cards
        - 1960-1961 (Box 85)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 85)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 85)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 85)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 85)
      - Clements Library
        - 1957-1958 (Box 85)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 85)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 85)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 85)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 85)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 85)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 85)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 85)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 85)
      - Colorado University
        - 1958-1961 (Box 85)
        - 1963-1968 (Box 85)
      - Columbia University
        - 1957-1958 (Box 85)
        - 1958-1963 (Box 85)
        - 1963-1967 (Box 85)
      - Commission on Obscenity and Pornography
        - Correspondence
          - January-June 1968 (Box 85)
          - July-December 1968 (Box 85)
          - January-August 1969 (Box 85)
          - September-December 1969 (Box 85)
          - January-April 1970 (Box 85)
          - May-August 1970 (Box 85)
          - September-December 1970 (Box 85)
          - January-June 1971 (Box 86)
        - Enabling Legislation (Box 86)
        - Staff (Box 86)
        - Wagman Personal (Box 86)
        - Minutes, 6 folders (Box 86)
        - Statements of Witnesses, 3 folders (Box 86)
        - Reports to the Commission
          - National Survey., 1 folder, 1 volume (Box 86)
          - Legal Aspects, 3 folders (Box 86)
          - Anti-Pornography Groups, 1 folder, 4 volumes (Box 87)
          - Sex Education, 2 folders (Box 87)
          - Adolescents, 3 folders (Box 87)
          - Movies and Rating System, 2 folders (Box 87)
          - Denmark and Sweden (Box 87)
          - Miscellanea, 2 folders, 1 volume (Box 87)
        - Miscellaneous reports, 2 folders, 2 volumes (Box 88)
        - Reprints of Journal Articles, 4 folders (Box 88)
        - Newspaper Clippings, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - Progress Report (Box 88)
        - Final Report
          - Positive Approaches Panel (Box 88)
          - Effects Panel, 2 folders (Box 88)
          - Legal Panel, 2 folders (Box 88)
          - Traffic and Distribution Panel (Box 89)
          - Findings and Recommendations (Box 89)
          - Draft, 2 folders, 1 volume (Box 89)
        - Charles H. Keating Report, 3 volumes (Box 89)
      - Committee on Library Automation (COLA), 1965-1966 (Box 89)
      - Complaints
        - 1958-1959 (Box 89)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 89)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 89)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 89)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 89)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 89)
        - 1965-1967 (Box 89)
      - Conference on Lifetime Reader, the Literary Art and the Library, 1966-1967 (Box 89)
      - Conference on Strengthening Library Services in Junior Colleges, 1963-1964 (Box 89)
      - Copyright Law
        - 1958-1959 (Box 89)
        - 1959-1962 (Box 89)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 89)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 89)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 89)
      - Cornell University
        - 1957-1962 (Box 89)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 89)
        - 1963-1968 (Box 89)
      - Council on Library Resources, Ford Foundation
        - 1957-1958 (Box 90)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 90)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 90)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 90)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 90)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 90)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 90)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 90)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 90)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 90)
      - CLR Board of Directors and Executive Committee
        - 1957-1958 (Box 90)
        - 1959-1965 (Box 91)
        - 1966-1972 (Box 92)
      - CLR Reports
        - 1957-1958 (Box 92)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 92)
        - 1959-1960, 2 folders (Box 93)
        - 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 93)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 93)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 93)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 93)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 93)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 93)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 94)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 94)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 94)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 94)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 94)
      - Dartmouth College, 1960-1961 (Box 94)
      - Dearborn Public Library, 1966-1967 (Box 94)
      - Detroit Public Library
        - 1957-1958 (Box 94)
        - 1958-1962 (Box 94)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 94)
        - 1965-1967 (Box 94)
      - Detroit University, 1958-1962 (Box 94)
      - Divisional Library Supervisors Meeting
        - 1962-1963 (Box 94)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 94)
      - Documents Expediting Project, 1958-1960 (Box 94)
      - Drexel Institute of Technology, 1957-1958 (Box 94)
      - Duke University
        - 1958-1959 (Box 94)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 94)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 94)
        - 1965-1967 (Box 94)
      - Early Modern English Dictionary, 1957-1958 (Box 94)
      - Eastern Michigan University
        - 1961-1962 (Box 94)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 94)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 94)
      - Exhibits
        - 1958-1965 (Box 94)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 94)
      - Faculty Appraisal of a University Library
        - 1963-1964 (Box 94)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 94)
      - Faculty Handbook, 1963 (Box 94)
      - Faculty Status for Librarians
        - 1957-1958 (Box 94)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 94)
        - 1961-1964 (Box 94)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 94)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 94)
      - Faculty Women's Club
        - 1958-1959 (Box 94)
      - Fines
        - 1959-1963 (Box 94)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 94)
      - Flint Junior College, 1958-1959 (Box 94)
      - Flint Public Library, 1965-1966 (Box 94)
      - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1957-1961 (Box 94)
      - General Motors Corp. Research Staff, 1957-1960 (Box 94)
      - Grand Valley State College, 1961-1962 (Box 94)
      - Greeting Cards, 1957-1958 (Box 94)
      - Hampshire College, 1966-1967 (Box 94)
      - Harvard University
        - 1957-1958 (Box 94)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 94)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 94)
      - Human Relations Area Files, 1957-1961 (Box 94)
      - Illinois University
        - 1957-1958 (Box 94)
        - 1958-1961 (Box 94)
        - 1962-1964 (Box 94)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 94)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 94)
      - Indiana University
        - 1959-1961 (Box 94)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 94)
        - 1963-1966 (Box 94)
      - Inquiries
        - 1957-1959 (Box 94)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 94)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 95)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 95)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 95)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 95)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 95)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 95)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 95)
      - Institute of Canadian-American Relations
        - 1963-1964 (Box 95)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 95)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 195T-1961 (Box 95)
      - International Congress of Orientalists, 1966-196T (Box 95)
      - Inter-University Communication Council
        - 1964-1965 (Box 95)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 95)
      - Invitations
        - 1957-1958 (Box 95)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 95)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 95)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 95)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 95)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 95)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 95)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 95)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 95)
      - Joint Committee of the ALA and the ABPC Committee on Reading Development
        - 1957-1958 (Box 95)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 95)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 95)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 95)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 95)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 95)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 95)
      - Joint Committee on the Union List of Serials, Subcommittee on World List of Serials, 1966-1967 (Box 95)
      - Kansas University
        - 1957-1961 (Box 95)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 95)
      - Kentucky University
        - 1957-1958 (Box 95)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 95)
      - Keys, 1958-1962 (Box 95)
      - Labadie Collection
        - 1958-1959 (Box 95)
        - 1959-1962 (Box 95)
        - 1962-1965 (Box 95)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 95)
      - Letters of Thanks
        - 1960-1962 (Box 95)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 95)
        - 1963-1965 (Box 95)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 95)
        - 1966-1969 (Box 95)
      - Library Buildings
        - 1962-1963 (Box 96)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 96)
      - Library Cooperation
        - 1957-1959 (Box 96)
        - 1959-1961 (Box 96)
      - Library Equipment, 1965-1966 (Box 96)
      - Library of Congress
        - 1957-1958 (Box 96)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 96)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 96)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 96)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 96)
        - 1962-1963, 2 folders (Box 96)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 96)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 96)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 96)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 96)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 96)
      - Library of Congress Russian Duplicates Exchange Program, 1957-1958 (Box 96)
      - Library Statistics
        - 1956-1958 (Box 97)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 97)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 97)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 97)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 97)
        - 1962-1964 (Box 97)
        - 1964-1967 (Box 97)
      - McAllister, Samuel W.
        - 1957-1959 (Box 97)
        - ALA, 1957-1958 (Box 97)
        - MLA, 1957-1959 (Box 97)
      - McCord, Dr. Carey, 1955-1958 (Box 97)
      - Marygrove College, 1957-1958 (Box 97)
      - Medical Library Resources Grant, 1966-1967 (Box 97)
      - Medlars Regional Center
        - 1965-1966 (Box 97)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Academy of Science, Arts and Letters
        - 1957-1958 (Box 97)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 97)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 97)
        - 1960-1962 (Box 97)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 97)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 97)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 97)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 97)
      - Michigan College Association, 1957-1961 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Council for Better Libraries
        - 1958-1960 (Box 97)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents, 1960-1961 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Daily and Daily Official Bulletin
        - 1960-1964 (Box 97)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Governor's Conference on Libraries, 1962-1963 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Historical Collections
        - 1957-1960 (Box 97)
        - 1960-1963 (Box 97)
        - 1963-1965 (Box 97)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 97)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Library Association
        - 1957-1958 (Box 97)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 97)
        - 1959-1962 (Box 97)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 97)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 97)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 97)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 97)
      - MLA Intellectual Freedom Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 97)
      - MLA Nominating Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 97)
      - Michigan Newspapers on Microfilm, 1957-1958 (Box 97)
      - Michigan State Library
        - 1957-1960 (Box 97)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 97)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 97)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 97)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 97)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 97)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 97)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 97)
      - Michigan State Study Advisory Committee
        - 1958-1959 (Box 98)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 98)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 98)
      - Michigan State University
        - 1957-1958 (Box 98)
        - 1958-1962 (Box 98)
      - Michigan University
        - 1960-1962 (Box 98)
        - 1962-1964 (Box 98)
        - 1964-1966 (Box 98)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 98)
      - Michigan University
        - Academic Affairs Advisory Council
          - 1962-1963 (Box 98)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 98)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 98)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 98)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 98)
        - Administrative Dean
          - 1958-1960 (Box 98)
          - 1960-1961 (Box 98)
          - 1961-1962 (Box 98)
          - 1962-1964 (Box 98)
          - 1965-1967 (Box 98)
        - Alumni, 1958-1966 (Box 98)
        - Association for Asian Studies
          - 1958-1959 (Box 98)
          - 1960-1963 (Box 98)
        - Audio-Visual Education Center
          - 1957-1959 (Box 98)
          - 1959-1961 (Box 98)
          - 1961-1962 (Box 98)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 98)
          - 1963-1965 (Box 98)
        - Azazels
          - 1957-1963 (Box 98)
          - 1963-1966 (Box 98)
        - Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1960-1962 (Box 98)
        - Bureau of School Services, 1962-1965 (Box 98)
        - Center for Chinese Studies, 1963-1964 (Box 98)
        - Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1965-1967 (Box 98)
        - Center for Japanese Studies
          - 1958-1963 (Box 98)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 98)
        - Center for Near and Middle Eastern Studies, 1962-1965 (Box 98)
        - Center for Near Eastern and North African Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 98)
        - Center for Russian Studies, 1962-1966 (Box 98)
        - Center for South and Southeast Asian Studies
          - 1962-1963 (Box 98)
          - 1966-1969 (Box 98)
        - College of Architecture and Design
          - 1957-1958 (Box 98)
          - 1958-1962 (Box 98)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 98)
        - College of Engineering, 1957-1965 (Box 98)
        - College of Literature, Science, and the Arts
          - 1958-1961 (Box 99)
          - 1961-1964 (Box 99)
          - 1966-1968 (Box 99)
          - Committee on Long Range Planning and Policy Recommendations
            - 1963-1964 (Box 99)
            - 1964-1965 (Box 99)
          - Library Committee
            - 1957-1961 (Box 99)
            - 1962-1963 (Box 99)
            - 1966-1967 (Box 99)
        - College of Pharmacy, 1965-1966 (Box 99)
        - Committee for the Study of Academic Data Procedures, 1965-1967 (Box 99)
        - Committee on College Relations, 1957-1959 (Box 99)
        - Committee on Computer Policies
          - 1964-1965 (Box 99)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 99)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 99)
        - Committee on University Publications Problems, 1963-1964 (Box 99)
        - Conferences, 1966-1967 (Box 99)
        - Conferences on Higher Education, 1958-1963 (Box 99)
        - Controller
          - 1957-1958 (Box 99)
          - 1958-1961 (Box 99)
          - 1961-1962 (Box 99)
          - 1962-1965 (Box 99)
        - Dean of Faculties, 1957-1962 (Box 99)
        - Dean of Women, 1958-1959 (Box 99)
        - Deans
          - 1957-1958 (Box 99)
          - 1958-1959 (Box 99)
          - 1959-1960 (Box 99)
          - 1960-1961 (Box 99)
          - 1961-1962 (Box 99)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 99)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 99)
          - 1964-1966 (Box 99)
          - 1966-1968 (Box 99)
        - Dearborn College
          - 1957-1958 (Box 99)
          - 1958-1959 (Box 99)
          - 1960-1963 (Box 99)
        - Department of Anthropology, 1965-1966 (Box 99)
        - Department of Botany, 1958-1961 (Box 99)
        - Department of Chemistry, 1958-1959 (Box 99)
        - Department of Classical Studies
          - 1957-1959 (Box 99)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 99)
        - Department of Economics, 1957-1961 (Box 99)
        - Department of English Language and Literature
          - 1957-1959 (Box 99)
          - 1965-1967 (Box 99)
        - Department of Far Eastern Languages and Literature, 1961-1963 (Box 99)
        - Department of Geography, 1957-1958 (Box 99)
        - Department of Geology, 1957-1958 (Box 99)
        - Department of History
          - 1957-1962 (Box 99)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 99)
        - Department of Journalism
          - 1957-1958 (Box 99)
          - 1958-1961 (Box 99)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 99)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 99)
        - Department of Library Science
          - 1957-1959 (Box 99)
          - 1959-1962 (Box 99)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 99)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 99)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 99)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 99)
        - Department of Mathematics
          - 1957-1962 (Box 99)
          - 1963-1965 (Box 99)
        - Department of Near Eastern Studies, 1957-1962 (Box 99)
        - Department of Political Science, 1958-1959 (Box 99)
        - Department of Psychology, 1961-1962 (Box 99)
        - Department of Romance Languages, 1957-1962 (Box 99)
        - Department of Slavic Languages and Literature
          - 1958-1962 (Box 99)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 99)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 99)
        - Extension Service, 1960-1970 (Box 99)
        - Faculty Library Center, 1961-1962 (Box 99)
        - Flint Senior College
          - 1957-1959 (Box 99)
          - 1959-1963 (Box 99)
        - General Library Building
          - 1957-1958 (Box 100)
          - 1958-1959 (Box 100)
          - 1959-1960 (Box 100)
          - 1960-1961 (Box 100)
          - 1961-1962 (Box 100)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 100)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 100)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 100)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 100)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 100)
          - Improvements
            - 1958-1960 (Box 100)
            - 1962-1963 (Box 100)
          - Projected Annex
            - 1962-1963 (Box 100)
            - 1963-1964 (Box 100)
            - 1964-1965 (Box 100)
            - 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 100)
            - 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 100)
          - Room Assignments, 1957-1963 (Box 100)
          - Space Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 100)
        - General Library Council
          - 1957-1959 (Box 100)
          - 1959-1962 (Box 100)
          - 1962-1965 (Box 100)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 100)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 100)
        - Graduate School
          - 1958-1959 (Box 100)
          - 1959-1960 (Box 100)
          - 1960-1962 (Box 100)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 100)
          - 1966-1967 (Box 100)
        - Health Sciences Information Center
          - 1964-1965 (Box 100)
          - 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 101)
          - 1966-1968 (Box 101)
        - Health Service, 1958-1960 (Box 101)
        - Institute for Social Research
          - 1958-1959 (Box 101)
          - 1960-1964 (Box 101)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 101)
          - 1965-1968 (Box 101)
        - Institute of Public Administration
          - 1960-1962 (Box 101)
          - 1962-1965 (Box 101)
        - Institute of Science and Technology
          - 1960-1962 (Box 101)
          - 1962-1965 (Box 101)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 101)
        - Inter-Institutional Cooperation, 1958-1959 (Box 101)
        - Joint Area and International Studies Committee
          - 1961-1962 (Box 101)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 101)
        - Lane Hall, 1960-1961 (Box 101)
        - Law Library, 1957-1960 (Box 101)
        - Libraries
          - 1960-1961 (Box 101)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 101)
          - 1964-1965 (Box 101)
          - 1965-1966 (Box 101)
          - 1966-1968 (Box 101)
        - Library
          - Accounts
            - 1957-1960 (Box 101)
            - 1960-1965 (Box 101)
            - 1965-1967 (Box 101)
            - Area Funds
              - 1961-1962 (Box 101)
              - 1962-1963 (Box 101)
              - 1963-1964 (Box 101)
              - 1964-1965 (Box 101)
              - 1965-1966 (Box 101)
              - 1966-1967 (Box 101)
            - Bureau of Government Replacement Fund 58L, 1959-1960 (Box 101)
            - Current Expense Account
              - 1957-1958 (Box 101)
              - 1958-1959 (Box 101)
              - 1959-1960 (Box 101)
              - 1960-1961 (Box 101)
              - 1961-1962 (Box 101)
              - 1962-1963 (Box 101)
              - 1963-1964 (Box 101)
              - 1964-1965 (Box 101)
              - 1965-1966 (Box 101)
              - 1966-1967 (Box 101)
            - General Book Account
              - 1957-1958 (Box 101)
              - 1958-1959 (Box 101)
              - 1959-1961 (Box 101)
              - 1961-1962 (Box 101)
              - 1962-1963 (Box 101)
              - 1963-1964 (Box 101)
              - 1964-1965 (Box 101)
              - 1965-1966 (Box 101)
              - 1966-1967 (Box 101)
            - Japanese Library Books, 1957-1958 (Box 101)
          - Acquisitions Department
            - 1964-1965 (Box 101)
            - 1965-1966 (Box 101)
            - 1966-1967 (Box 101)
          - Administration, 1958-1962 (Box 101)
          - Book Selection Department
            - 1957-1958 (Box 101)
            - 1958-1959 (Box 101)
            - 1959-1960 (Box 101)
            - 1960-1961 (Box 102)
            - 1961-1962 (Box 102)
            - 1962-1963 (Box 102)
            - 1963-1964 (Box 102)
            - 1964-1965 (Box 102)
            - 1965-1967 (Box 102)
          - Budget
            - 1959-1960 (Box 102)